MUSTAFA TUFAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

mail@mustafatufan.com.tr

+90 538 018 95 16

PERSONEL

OBJECTIVES

🏆 In 5 years: Being part of best products.

In 10 years: Being top level software engineer.

L In 20 years: Being C level executive.

SKILLS

Software Development

Database Development

Mobile App & Game Development 🙀

SUMMARY

I am Mustafa Tufan, the software engineering graduate. I am a software developer who is always in pursuit of designing the best software & writing the best line of codes. I am passionate about details, I continuously think how to improve myself, where I am & what I do. I always love the small piece of improvements that make products better & people's life easy. In business & socially, I believe in justice & individualism.

At the moment, I am developing with Java, J2EE, JSP, JSF, MSSQL, Sybase, Primefaces, Jasper Reports, Tomcat & Wildfly servers in Infina Software. On an ordinary day, I am responsible to create, code & test Java beans, stored SQL procedures & functions, Primefaces JSF pages & Jasper Reports designs. I developed & published Android apps & Unity3D games in the past. I also have experience on how to use version control & project management systems. I like using & working with high-end tech products.

I am good at games, puzzles, abstract thinking & logic. I do not smoke. I am a social drinker. I watch sci-fi & fantasy movies & TV shows. I play mostly story-based video games. I can not say that I am good at books but I read wiki pages a lot. In 2018 I will learn French.

EXPERIENCE



Software Developer, Infina Software

Mar. 2016 - Current

Worked in a team that develops & supports Infleks Operation project that is a full automation system for investment banks. AK Investment & Seker Invest are using Infleks Operation. Mainly committed on Accounting, Fund & Customer modules.



Intern, Emeltek Software

Jan. - Jun. 2015

Designed & developed Android games those Rolling & Breaking Stone & KELİME BUL. includes Google Play Game Services, Unity Ads & Admob.



Intern, Netix IT

Oct. 2012 - Sep. 2013

Developed an Android app that named Encrypted SMS which allows you send & receive SMS with AES encryption.



Intern, Dreamharvesters Game Studio

Jul. - Sep. 2012

Designed & developed a mini 3D game for LanistaWars project. Also programmed a tool that helps to edit subtitle texts.



Independent Android Developer & Publisher, Android Turşusu

2011 - 2013

Developed & published some Android apps like Bilişim Bilgi Yarışması & Afacan. All apps totally downloaded over 100,000.

EDUCATION



Capital Markets & Stock Exchange, Marmara University

2017 - 2018

3 terms non-thesis master's degree program includes finance theory, economics analysis & finance mathematics.



Software Engineering, Firat University

2010 - 2015

8 terms software engineering bachelor's degree program includes object oriented programming, database systems, data structures, game & mobile app development, Al basics, software quality assurance & testing.



Information Technology, Gaziemir Anadolu Technical High School

2006 - 2010

4 years high school education includes computer, programming & database basics.